EL MEHDI ER. RAJI

+212 651 925 000

elmehdiworkemail@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mehdi-erraji
Agadir, Souss Massa 80000 Morocco
220 Drarga Agadir

Jun 2022

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Technologically-inclined IT Service Desk Technician with more than 3 years of experience with hardware support and maintenance of technical equipment. Proven analytical and problem-solving abilities for prioritizing and executing tasks in high-pressure environment. Working technical knowledge of current operating systems, software, and standards.

SKILLS

- · Hardware repair
- · Read technical manuals
- Support end-users
- Motivation

- Testing and debugging
- Resolve technical problems
- Multitasking
- team work

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer Intern, The National Electricity and Water Office, Mar 2022 - Jul 2022, Agadir

- Built front-end of applications through appealing visual design.
- Presented innovative ideas to improve systems, processes, or services and new perspectivesbased on independent research.
- Researched problems discovered in testing or production and developed solutions.
- Design and create data bases.
- Create a full stack web application using PHP stack.

Internship Student, Moroccan Packaging Company - Fantasia, Apr 2021 - Jul 2021, Inzegan

- Answered incoming calls and directed messages to correct party.
- Supported office staff by processing correspondence, documents, and reports. Scheduled
- meetings and assisted in making travel arrangements.
- Communicated regularly with external and internal customers to understand and meet theirneeds.
- Reviewed accounts daily to determine the areas in need of improvement and strategies for correcting faults.

EDUCATION

Certification, Software engineering

Alx Africa

Bachelor's degree, computer science

Ibn Zohr University - Agadir, Morocco

Feb 2023 - Feb 2024

Sept 2022 - Dec 2024

Superior School of Technology - Guelmim, Morocco

University degree in technology, Computer science

Haj Seid Hight school - Agadir, Morocco

High School Diploma, science math Jul 2020

LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native French: Advanced English: Advanced